<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<pages>
    <item>
        <title>In a few words</title>
        <category>About</category>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[
            <h3>Welcomango? Is that a fruit company?</h3>
            <p>Hmm... nope. And we're definitely not the "Uber of tourism" either</p>
            <hr />
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p>As travelers ourselves, we enjoy visiting places through the eyes of a friend&nbsp;who know the city.&nbsp;But since we don't have friends all over the world, it is unfortunately not something we could do. That's the reason why we made Welcomango. We wanted to build a community which could recreate this experience anywhere, anytime, with people willing to share their time as well as&nbsp;their&nbsp;perception of the place they live in.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
            <h5 style="text-align: center;">And that's what Welcomango is. A platform where you can find people eager to show you how they&nbsp;experience&nbsp;and love their city. And where you can also share&nbsp;a vision of your own city by proposing an experience.</h5>
            <p>But don't get us wrong, the people you'll find here are no professional guides and they don't claim to be. In fact, they are not guides at all. They are&nbsp;the human face of&nbsp;their city and&nbsp;we enforce this idea&nbsp;by allowing&nbsp;anyone registered on Welcomango to&nbsp;propose an experience. Because we believe traveling is a two sides adventure where you should both take and share.</p>
            <p>And because we believe any work deserve compensation, we let&nbsp;our users decide if they want to be rewarded for their work and how. So they can ask for a financial&nbsp;compensation but&nbsp;they can also&nbsp;ask you to bring something from your place to enforce the cultural exchange.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </item>


    <item>
        <title>Thanks</title>
        <category>About</category>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[
            <h1>Thanks</h1>
            <hr />
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p>A list of the different free&nbsp;tools we used that helped us to build this awesome website</p>
            <p><a href="https://symfony.com/">The Symfony project</a>: The main framework of the project. We could not say here how much we love Symfony so we're going to let you check by yourself</p>
            <p><a href="http://mynameismatthieu.com/WOW/">Wow.js</a>: Funny little tool which provides good looking animation. Plus the website contains Doge, how awesome</p>
            <p><a href="http://fontawesome.io">Fontawesome</a>: Which help us have these wonderful little icons everywhere</p>
            <p><a href="http://dimsemenov.com/plugins/magnific-popup/">Magnific Popup</a>:&nbsp;For the great image slideshow on the experience page</p>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p>We would also like to give a special thanks to Riccardo David Marriano and Daniel Hernandez without whom this idea would not exist. Another special thanks to Karoliina&nbsp;Lohiniva for the help and support. And of course to anyone would support and help us&nbsp;to make Welcomango alive.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>How to</title>
        <category>How To</category>
        <content>
        <![CDATA[
            <blockquote>
                <p style="letter-spacing: 0.14px;">Welcomango is aiming to propose a simple and intuitive experience so that travelers&nbsp;ands&nbsp;local have a chance to meet and share their perception of a&nbsp;place. Bored of traveling with guides or blog post visited a million time? Welcomango allows you to&nbsp;explore a destination through the eyes of a local in a few click. Follow the five steps to get started!</p>
                <p style="letter-spacing: 0.14px;">&nbsp;</p>
            </blockquote>
            <h3 style="letter-spacing: 0.14px; text-align: center;">1 - Type your next destination</h3>
            <p style="letter-spacing: 0.14px;"><img style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" src="../../../../bundles/welcomangocore/images/graphics/step1.min.svg" alt="" width="390" height="245" /></p>
            <p style="letter-spacing: 0.14px;">&nbsp;</p>
            <p style="letter-spacing: 0.14px;">How could it be simpler? If you already have a trip planned or if you already know&nbsp;what is your next destination, just type the name of the city in the search box! If the welcomango community&nbsp;has planted its seeds there, the locals should show up.&nbsp;</p>
            <p style="letter-spacing: 0.14px;"><em>No idea yet?:&nbsp;</em>Go to the&nbsp;<a href="../../../../experiences">experience page</a>&nbsp;and search by tags or dates to find people with common interests&nbsp;willing to&nbsp;show you how their city can be interesting in a specific way!</p>
            <h2 style="letter-spacing: 0.14px; text-align: center;">&nbsp;</h2>
            <h3 style="letter-spacing: 0.14px; text-align: center;">2 - Find a local who match your interests</h3>
            <p><img style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" src="../../../../bundles/welcomangocore/images/graphics/step2.min.svg" alt="" width="390" height="245" /></p>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p>Anyone registered on the website can propose what we call an <strong>experience</strong>. We do not control experiences, we do not exert any kind of influence and we only moderate in case of&nbsp;very inappropriate language or images.</p>
            <p>These experiences reflect one's unique perception of a city. It may be through a&nbsp;passion like arts, sports, nature, food, or it may simply be the way this person lives and enjoys his city. We believe everybody has something to share about his place as soon as he has lived there for some time. That's why anyone can become a member of the community and propose an experience (and if you doubt this, go read <a href="../../../../read/proposing-an-experience">Me? Showing my city?</a>&nbsp;right now!)</p>
            <p>Once you found the perfect match, send him a booking request with a message and some details about the meeting&nbsp;(such as how many persons will be there and for how long. We like the idea that people can manage their time the way they want). As soon as it's accepted,&nbsp;things can become serious!&nbsp;</p>
            <h3 style="text-align: center;">3 - Book and meet the person and enjoy your visit</h3>
            <p><img style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" src="../../../../bundles/welcomangocore/images/graphics/step3.min.svg" alt="" width="390" height="245" /></p>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p><strong>Now it's all about the fun!</strong> Decide of a meeting point and enjoy a unique visit of your destination!</p>
            <p>You know better that us, it's not only about the city but&nbsp;mostly<strong> about the people</strong>. And now you have the possibility to enjoy both without having to fight cultural bareers or shyness.</p>
            <p>Eventually, pay a contribution to your new local friend according to what was decided and go back home richer than ever.</p>
            <h3 style="text-align: center;">4 -&nbsp;Give a feedback to the person you met</h3>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p>Welcomango as we dream it is only made of super nice people. But some might not be as optimistic as we are. So we give you the opportunity to give a feedback about the person you met.&nbsp;Although, we are not fond of rating systems and we don't want the travelers to become overpowered judges while the locals would fall in some sort of servitude. That's why <strong>both locals and travelers can rate each others</strong>. This way people can learn more about how a potential visitor is and make sure things are going to be alright.</p>
            <h3 style="text-align: center;">5 - Propose&nbsp;an experience in your own city&nbsp;</h3>
            <p><img style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" src="../../../../bundles/welcomangocore/images/graphics/step5.min.svg" alt="" width="390" height="245" /></p>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p>We would all love to be travelers 24/7, all year long. But it's not the reality for most of us. So while you are back home, planning on your next trip, how about giving some of your time to<strong> propose an experience in your own city</strong>?</p>
            <p>We all have something to show about our place and you are no exception, you just need opportunities to share this knowledge. Welcomango allows you to define&nbsp;a very precise period during which you are available whether&nbsp;it's only on saturday afternoon or&nbsp;during&nbsp;work days in the early morning (for those who love hiking, running or photographing).&nbsp;</p>
            <p>Convinced? Time to get started!</p>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <div class="text-center"><a class="btn btn-primary" href="../../../../experiences">Search for an experience </a> <strong>or</strong> <a class="btn btn-primary" href="../../../../experience/create">create your own!</a></div><br/>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>Proposing an experience</title>
        <category>How To</category>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[
            <h3>Me guide? But I ain't got nothing to show!</h3>
            <h5>Proposing an experience of your city, a not&nbsp;as complicate task as you imagine it</h5>
            <hr />
            <p>Most of the time when we suggested the idea of Welcomango to travelers, adventurers or even random friends who like to travel from time to time, they loved the idea. But when it came to proposing a tour of their city, a lot of them had the same answer:</p>
            <blockquote>
                <p class="text-primary"><em>Me? But I don't know&nbsp;anything&nbsp;about this city!&nbsp;What could I show? people would get bored!</em></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Well, that the whole point of Welcomango. It's not because you don't know when your city was build, who&nbsp;was the last mayor and when the main&nbsp;square was built that you don't have anything to give to travelers. Actually, <strong>that's even better that way!</strong></p>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p><img style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" src="../../../../bundles/welcomangocore/images/graphics/step5.min.svg" alt="" width="390" height="245" /></p>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p>You may ignore it, but you actually know a lot about your city. And when I say a lot, it's A LOT! You've probably been around for some time and I am sure you&nbsp;experienced the city in many ways. Let us show you what you probably already did:</p>
            <ul style="list-style-type: circle;">
                <li>You got lost in your city. And discovered some weird spots that are still in your mind</li>
                <li>You had a marvelous dinner with friends at this super cool place which you loved</li>
                <li>You played with your basketball team in&nbsp;a full of screet-art area which blew your mind</li>
                <li>You&nbsp;shopped in this really cute shop,&nbsp;lost in the suburb, which sells such awesome items</li>
                <li>You had a drink (or more?) with people you like and enjoyed the music in this underground place you would have never suspected to exist</li>
                <li>Talking about music, you probably went to see concert in a pub and discovered a magical band</li>
            </ul>
            <p>And of course, <strong>you lived the city</strong>. You got used to its public transport delay. You worked or studied in a specific place with a great&nbsp;sandwich-bar which fulfilled your stomach so many times&nbsp;without killing your budget. If you've been living here for a long time maybe you also know this place where your grand father used to paint. And <strong>the beauty of this is that everywhere you go, you write little&nbsp;stories</strong>, you experience the city, its habits, its culture, and that gives you plenty of anecdotes to tell.</p>
            <p>See the point? If you like the place where you live it's because you make it beautiful.</p>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <h5 class="text-primary text-center">You already have something to show,&nbsp;and that's exactly what we want&nbsp;you&nbsp;to share.</h5>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p style="text-align: left;">Now, think about it the other way around. Read what is listed above and imagine yourself discovering a new place through these spots. Wouldn't it be awesome? Sit with someone living in the city in a bar he randomly discovered? Go to a concert in a place that doesn't even have a Facebook page? See where this person's grand father used to fight for revolution? How exciting right?</p>
            <p>I'm sure you now understand why we wanted Welcomango to exist and what it really is. In a few words: <strong>It's about experiencing places through people and their perspective of the place they inhabit</strong></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>The Team</title>
        <category>About</category>
        <content>
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>About Us</h1>
            <hr />
            <blockquote>
                <p><span style="line-height: normal;">Young, cheerful and determined, we want Welcomango to become real because we would be the first to use it. Travelers, explorers and discoverers, we are the brain and the hands of this project. Join us in the venture.&nbsp;</span></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p><span style="line-height: normal;">&nbsp;<img class="wow fadeInUp animated" style="border-radius: 50%; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" src="../../../../bundles/welcomangocore/images/team/Eliot.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="200" /></span></p>
            <h3 style="text-align: center;"><span style="line-height: normal;">Eliot</span></h3>
            <p>Born in Lyon, France, Eliot has a double background in Political Science and IT. Fond of music and a musician himself,&nbsp;, he uses his artistic skills in photography and design. During his free time, he can floor you in badminton. Who said nobody is perfect? He lived in Taiwan, Brussels, Geneva, and the US, worked for web agencies and International Organizations for some time before deciding to forge his own way.&nbsp;Leading the Welcomango project,&nbsp;he manages&nbsp;a wide range of aspects of the project from development to management and social&nbsp;outreach.&nbsp;</p>
            <p>&nbsp;</p>
            <p><img class="wow fadeInLeft animated" style="border-radius: 50%; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" src="../../../../bundles/welcomangocore/images/team/Jean-Baptiste.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="200" /></p>
            <h3 style="text-align: center;">Jean-Baptiste</h3>
            <p style="text-align: left;">Born in Lyon,&nbsp;Jean-Baptiste made his way in the web development field with his own teeth! Not only typing on his keyboard he&nbsp;loves hitting things that make sound (Especially brazilians ones, ever heard of Batucada?). JB is the lead&nbsp;developper and&nbsp;is making magic with his computer to support this cute little website. Any tech question? He's the one!</p>
            <p style="text-align: left;"><img class="wow fadeInDown animated" style="border-radius: 50%; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" src="../../../../bundles/welcomangocore/images/team/Matthieu.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="200" /></p>
            <h3 style="text-align: center;">Matthieu&nbsp;</h3>
            <p>Born in Besan&ccedil;on (France) in 1987, Matthieu holds a BA degree in Communication studies and a MA degree in Human Rights. He began to travel during his studies doing a communication internship in Canada before going to the Netherlands for a year with the Erasmus exchange programme. In 2010, Matthieu volunteered in Burkina Faso for a year where he decided to give a new perspective to his career. He was selected to be part of the Erasmus Mundus Human Rights Practice MA programme run as a joint partnership between Gothenburg University (Sweden), Roehampton University (UK) and Troms&oslash; University (Norway). This programme gave him the opportunity to have some professional experience in the UK, Norway and Denmark. He is in charge of the communication aspect of the project, definitely the coolest guy you'll have the chance to meet. If you ignore the fact he supports a forgotten french foot team called&nbsp;FCSM.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </item>

    <item>
        <title>Legal</title>
        <category>About</category>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[
            All rights reserved
            ]]>
        </content>
    </item>
</pages>


